https://www.ewsolutions.com/about/privacy-cookies/

First Name*Last Name*Email*
PhoneMessage*EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
EWSolutions Privacy Policy
EWSolutions is committed to respecting your privacy. This statement applies with respect to information we collect from http://www.ewsolutions.com/ and any other sites on the World Wide Web owned and/or operated by EWSolutions. This statement is part of our Terms of Use and is subject to all of its terms. Below is information regarding the commitment of EWSolutions to protect the personal data of its website visitors.
The term “personal data” includes any information that enables you to be identified, such as your name, physical address, e-mail address, and phone number.
1. Nature of the Data Collected and Purpose of the Data Processing
When you access this website, EWSolutions collects the IP address of the computer you are using to browse the site. If this address is a “static” or fixed IP address, EWSolutions could in certain circumstances be able to identify you, theoretically, and therefore, this type of information could be considered personal data. However, EWSolutions only collects this type of information to compile usage statistics on an anonymous basis. EWSolutions does not collect IP address data to identify you.
Apart from your IP address, no personal data is transmitted when accessing this Website. Unless you submit personal data about yourself by filling in a form on the website or by sending us an e-mail, we will not maintain any other personal data as a result of your access and usage of the site.
The website invites you to register with us on-line, by providing information through a form page. We use the information you submit by registering to send you customized marketing information by post, on-line download or e-mail. You may request to cease receiving such information at any time following registration. You may request to be removed from our e-mail list by sending an email to unsubscribe@EWSolutions.com with the word “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the email subject line or by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email. You may request to be removed from our postal mailing list by sending an e-mail message to unsubscribe@EWSolutions.com or by sending a letter to:
EWSolutionsAttn: PrivacyP.O. Box 70Hinsdale, IL 60521Fax: 630.920.0008info@EWSolutions.com
The site may also require you to register to enjoy certain services provided through the site, such as on-line support or on-line education. The information provided in the context of registering for these services is collected to respond to your inquiry, process an order, to provide you with access to specific account information, or to enable us to provide you the aforementioned on-line services securely through password protection.
In addition, to better understand the needs of the visitors of this website and to adapt the website to these needs, we occasionally conduct on-line surveys. Participation in these surveys is optional. The data collected through these surveys is used for statistical analysis of visitor preferences, EWSolutions services, EWSolutions products or product category assessments and for direct marketing purposes.
2. Disclosure of Personal Data
Unless we tell you otherwise, we do not sell or rent your personal data to any third parties. When involved in a joint marketing partnership, EWSolutions may share information which you have submitted to us with the partner company which is subject to applicable non-disclosure obligations.
3. Use of “Cookies”
This website might send “cookies” to your computer to better serve you with more tailored information when you return to the website. A cookie is a small element of data that can be sent by our website to your browser and stored on your hard drive, not on EWSolutions’ website. Cookies do not collect information about visitors. Unless you input your Personal Data onto our website you cannot be identified and you remain anonymous. You can set most browsers to tell you when you are sent a cookie and to refuse to receive it.
4. Security of Your Data
EWSolutions takes all commercially reasonable precautions to adequately prevent others from freely accessing the information you provide or that we compile. As you are no doubt aware, however, despite these precautions, zealous hackers may wrongfully gain access to this information. Although such unauthorized access is unlikely, we feel obligated to inform you of the risk and advise you that EWSolutions is not liable for any damages caused by such unauthorized access.
5. Third Party Sites
This policy only addresses our activities from our servers. Other sites (including those that we link to within an advertisement banner or otherwise, and third party sites or services which we co-brand) may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed by this policy.
6. Your Right to Access, Correction, and Erasure
You have the right to ask EWSolutions about the information we hold about you. In addition, you have the right to correct or delete any information we hold about you. If you wish to know which information EWSolutions holds about you or if you wish to correct and update this information, please contact us at:
EWSolutionsAttn: PrivacyP.O. Box 70Hinsdale, IL 60521Fax: 630.920.0008info@EWSolutions.com
EWSolutions endeavors to honor your request within four weeks of receipt. If you want us to delete your private data and unsubscribe yourself from any mailing list or e-mail list in the future, we will attend to your demand within four weeks of receiving your e-mail or letter.
7. Changes to the Privacy Policy
This policy may be amended at any time, so please check back periodically.
Send All Correspondences EWSolutions PO Box 70 Hinsdale, IL 60522
© Since 1997 to the present – Enterprise Warehousing Solutions, Inc. (EWSolutions). All Rights Reserved
